Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Painting a New Future
Episode 60
Our reinforcements have arrived.
So many Weslies…
This is unbelievable.
To think there are so many
versions of me from different worlds.
I’ll let a villain like you
see for yourself
the power of justice from across different worlds.
How amusing. But to me,
it’s nothing more than going from one ant to a whole swarm of them.
Little ants,
vanish, every single one of you.
Outrageous!
Taste my power!
Pleasant Iron Fist!
Overestimating yourself.
No way…
I’ll catch you.
Watch this!
Is that all you’ve got?
Sonic Sky-Splitting Slash!
You’ve made me very angry.
None of you are escaping.
Wherever the sword flashes, there lies the path home.
Matrix Beam Cannon!
Pixel Blade!
Roar of the Water Dragon!
Don’t forget
this place
is my territory.
What’s happening?
I can’t seem to move.
Me neither.
Us too.
In the face of absolute power, your struggles are all in vain.
Become nourishment for me, all of you.
Our energy is being drained away.
The disparity in power between us is like heaven and earth.
Yet, there is a solution: with wills united and merged,
and every bone and sinew fused as one, even mountains may be shaken!
I understand.
Please channel your energy into my wings.
I don’t fully understand it,
but I think this method looks really cool.
Here goes.
Then accept our energy.
Weslie.
Thank you all for your trust.
Let’s put an end to
this farce together.
No…it shouldn’t be like this.
I am the ruler of this world.
It’s a boomerang.
You think a little gadget like that can hurt—
Wolffy!
At a moment as important as this,
how could I, King Wolffy, possibly be absent?
Let us show you
the true power of Weslie and Wolffy!
No…
I am the chosen protagonist!
It is impossible for me to fail!
Planie, you did it!
I finally succeeded in saving our world.
I…I’m back.
Weslie.
This is…
Big Sister, welcome home.
I…
Xi Huahua.
Mommy, look.
Green Green Grassland has been restored too.
You all did a wonderful job.
That’s great! We did it.
Mr. Slowy, all the other worlds are recovering.
Only theirs is still fading away.
Is there anything we can do?
I was thinking about the Xilan Tree.
The Xilan Tree possesses a power called Spark.
Perhaps every world has its own Spark.
Peach’s world
is facing its current crisis because its Spark has gone out.
If we want to save them,
we have to help them find the Spark.
The Spark?
We’ve worked so hard for so long…
It was all in vain after all.
Is that our final destination?
Stop looking.
In the end, we cannot change our fate of fading.
That is…
Don’t give up.
Why are you here?
We promised to help you, and we certainly won’t go back on our word.
It’s dangerous for you to be here.
You might fade away along with us.
You can’t give up.
Listen to me.
You need to feel the power that belongs to you.
Feel…our power.
You may have forgotten, but think of other worlds.
They, too, once faced crises.
But in the end, they all used their own strength to protect their respective worlds.
The power of courage.
The power of sacrifice.
The power of unity.
Because of this, their worlds were reborn.
Even after being destroyed, they could recover.
That is the power of their worlds.
The key to saving your world lies within yourselves.
That power will surely lead everyone to hope.
What is the power of our world?
The power of our world…
Could it be…
that the power of our world is…
I can feel it.
Let’s do it together.
It’s so beautiful.
Is this what their world truly looks like?
Thank you for guiding us
and helping us find our own power.
It’s so great to have met you all.
Let’s not stop creating.
For the sake of our world.
The weather is so nice.
It really is.
Finished the drawing.
Let me see.
Congratulations on the new king’s ascension.
Take a look at mine.
I’m done drawing.
I’m done too.
It’s so beautiful.
Sparky, what are you drawing?
Come and admire my masterpiece.
Come to think of it,
why was it only Weslies who appeared back then?
Yeah.
I’d like to know that too.
Because Weslie was the first one we called out for.
Will you think of me first next time?
Let’s hang up all the drawings.
We really have to say goodbye this time.
So, will we be able to meet again?
Of course we will.
But how will we meet without the rifts?
As long as we believe, we will definitely meet again.
End